Guide to the Chautauqua County Republican Party Committee minute book, 1855-1912.
Chautauqua County Republican Party Committee minute book, 1855-1912.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Chautauqua County Republican Party Committee minute book, 1855-1912.
1945
Chautauqua County Republican Party Committee.
1 reel positive, 1 reel negative microfilm.
Minutes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Minutes of annual conventions of the Chautauqua County Republican Party, with a history of the party in Chautauqua County.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Minutes of annual conventions of the Chautauqua County Republican Party, with a history of the party in Chautauqua County.
Minutes that do not contain the names of the chairman and secretaries are marked with an asterisk.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Chautauqua County Republican Party Committee.; Republican Party (Chautauqua County, N.Y.)
Subjects:
Politics, Practical--New York (State)--Chautauqua County.
Places:
Chautauqua County (N.Y.)--Politics and government.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
NOTES
Related collection: Joseph McGinnies. Papers, #1943.
Related collection: Samuel Frederick Nixon. Papers, #1944.
CONTAINER LIST
- W.M. Lett, A.W. McKinstry, Secretaries; Geo. A. Green, Chairman, Sept. 8, 1855 (Reel 1)
- James Parker, Daniel Sherman, Secretaries; John H. Pray, Chairman, Oct. 12, 1855 (Reel 1)
- F.W. Palmer, W. McKinstry, Secretaries; J.H. Pray, Chairman, Oct. 17, 1856 (Reel 1)
- J.F. Smith, A.A. Atherly, Secretaries; James Parker, Chairman, Sept. 15, 1858 (Reel 1)
- O. Benedict, Chairman; C.D. Sackett, E.H. Jenner, Secretaries, Sept. 23, 1859 (Reel 1)
- Jeremiah Mann, Chairman; C.D. Sackett, A.W. McKinstry, Secretaries, Sept. 21, 1860 (Reel 1)
- O. Benedict, Chairman; G.M. Abell, E.H. Jenner, C.D. Angell, Secretaries, Sept. 27, 1861 (Reel 1)
- Charles Kennedy, Chairman; C.D. Angell, M.C. Rice, Secretaries, Oct. 10, 1862 (Reel 1)
- W.L. Sessions, Chairman; Geo. W. Ten, Jr., M.C. Rice, Secretaries, Oct. 14, 1863 (Reel 1)
- Julien Williams, Chairman; B.F. Skinner, J.R. Robertson, Secretaries, Sept. 16, 1864 (Reel 1)
- N. Scott, Chairman; C.E. Bishop, R. Willing, Secretaries, Oct. 4, 1865 (Reel 1)
- Jas. Sheward, Chairman; C.D. Angell, C.E. Bishop, Secretaries, Sept. 20, 1866 (Reel 1)
- Hiram Smith, Chairman; E.H. Jenner, John J. Aldrich, Secretaries, Sept. 27, 1867 (Reel 1)
- Asa S. Couch, Chairman; John Aldrich, L.C. Warren, Secretaries, Sept. 24, 1868 (Reel 1)
- John Hall, Chairman; A.B. Fletcher, F.J. Bly, Secretaries, Oct. 6, 1869 (Reel 1)
- *Minutes tell how conventioneers listened to claims of rival delegates and decided which ones should be seated, Sept. 10, 1870 (Reel 1)
- *, Oct. 2, 1871 (Reel 1)
- A. Hazeltine, Chairman; R.E. Sheldon, W.S. Gleason, Secretaries, Oct. 2, 1872 (Reel 1)
- *, Oct. 1, 1873 (Reel 1)
- Orson Stiles, Chairman; Louis McKinstry, J.J. Aldrich, Secretaries, Sept. 25, 1874 (Reel 1)
- L. Risley, Chairman; Louis McKinstry, A.M. Clark, Secretaries, Sept. 21, 1875 (Reel 1)
- *, Sept. 1, 1876 (Reel 1)
- *, Sept. 24, 1877 (Reel 1)
- H.I. Ames, Chairman; L. McKinstry, John A. Hall, Secretaries, Sept. 21, 1878 (Reel 1)
- *, Sept. 9, 1879 (Reel 1)
- P.M. Miller, Chairman; George Sheldon, Daniel H. Post, Secretaries, Aug. 11, 1880 (Reel 1)
- Jerome B. Fisher, Chairman; J.M. McWharf, J.J. Aldrich, Secretaries, Aug. 23, 1881 (Reel 1)
- J.H. Monroe, Chairman; E.J. Sweetland, K.J. Forbes, Secretaries, Sept. 28, 1882 (Reel 1)
- H.C. Lake, Chairman; F.A. Hall, F.W. Hyde, Secretaries, Oct. 4, 1883 (Reel 1)
- *, Aug. 5, 1884 (Reel 1)
- *, Sept. 15, 1885 (Reel 1)
- *, Sept. 4, 1886 (Reel 1)
- *, Sept. 17, 1887 (Reel 1)
- *, Aug. 10, 1888 (Reel 1)
- *, Sept. 10, 1889 (Reel 1)
- *, Sept. 10, 1890 (Reel 1)
- *, Aug. 11, 1891 (Reel 1)
- *, July 29, 1892 (Reel 1)
- *, Aug. 29, 1893 (Reel 1)
- *, Aug. 7, 1894 (Reel 1)
- *, Aug. 27, 1895 (Reel 1)
- *, Aug. 11, 1896 (Reel 1)
- *, July 20-21, 1897 (Reel 1)
- *, July 7, 1898 (Reel 1)
- *, June 27, 1899 (Reel 1)
- *Speech by S. Fred Nixon, candidate for nomination as the Republican candidate for governor, June 27, 1900 (Reel 1)
- *, July 2, 1901 (Reel 1)
- *, July 1, 1902 (Reel 1)
- *, July 1, 1903 (Reel 1)
- *Speech by S. Fred Nixon praising the Roosevelt administration, July 7, 1904 (Reel 1)
- *Semi-centennial anniversary of the Republican party in Chautauqua county. Louis McKinstry gives a brief sketch of the early history of the Republican party, followed by a series of brief speeches; long detailed account of the struggle for nomination as county coroner between Dr. Illston and Dr. Bowers., Aug. 9, 1905 (Reel 1)
- *, June 26, 1906 (Reel 1)
- *, July 2, 1907 (Reel 1)
- *, May 25, 1908 (Reel 1)
- *, June 22, 1909 (Reel 1)
- Charles H. Wicks, Chairman; J.R. Douglas, Secretary., July 8, 1910 (Reel 1)
- Charles H. Wicks, Chairman; H.R. Mason, Secretary. Minutes of the Republican Party Committee meeting of Chautauqua County; contain rules for procedure., Feb. 8, 1912 (Reel 1)
- Charles Wicks, Chairman; H.R. Mason, Secretary, Mar. 1, 1912 (Reel 1)
- Charles Wicks, Chairman; H.R. Mason, Secretary, Apr. 4, 1912 (Reel 1)